webmarketinggroup.co.uk 2018-05-01

# Privacy Policy - WMG

**Approach to Privacy**

We are committed to protecting your personal information and take your right to privacy very seriously.  
This Privacy Policy is applicable to this website and to other websites owned and operated by Webevents Limited trading as WMG. You must read and accept all of this Privacy Policy before you may become a user of this website. By accepting this Privacy Policy you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy.

 **Overview**

This Privacy Policy describes the information we collect about you and what may happen to that information. When you enter your information into a form on our website we will collect personally identifiable information about you (your “Information”). Some of your Information may be disclosed to third parties and used by us and third parties. We will never sell or rent your personal information to third parties except as described in this Privacy Policy.

If you do not agree to your Information being used or disclosed in this way, please do not use our website.

 **Information Collection**

We may collect information from you including your name and telephone number that is necessary to provide our services. Should you contact us by email, telephone or send us correspondence, we may collect such information into a file that is specific to you.

Like many websites, we may also automatically receive general information that is contained in our server log files, such as your IP address and cookie information.

 **Use of Your Information**

We will use your Information to provide our services to you. You agree that we may use your Information to contact you for purposes including but not limited to discussing our products and services, targeted advertisements and communications relevant to your use of this website. You agree that we may use your Information to track and target your interests in order to enhance your experience on our website, to improve our website content and services, customise our website’s content and layout, analyse usage of our website and to improve our marketing efforts. We will use your Information in this way to improve our website and tailor it to better meet your specific needs.

 **Disclosure of Your Information**

We will never sell or rent your Information to third parties except as described in this Privacy Policy. We may aggregate the information you send to us with other data (so that you cannot be identified) and use that aggregated data for administrative purposes and/or share it with third parties or related organisations, including but not limited to advertising organisations for marketing and promotional purposes.  
We may employ the services of third party service providers in certain aspects of our operations and to help us deliver information and services. Depending on the services performed, some of these providers may be provided with your Information and we will take reasonable steps to ensure that these third party service providers are obligated to protect your Information on our behalf.

 **Legal Disclaimer**

Though we make every effort to preserve users’ privacy, we may need to disclose your Information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current or pending judicial proceeding, a court order, an investigation of unlawful activity or activity that may expose us or you to legal liability.

 **Security**

We use reasonable endeavours to safeguard the confidentiality of your Information, to keep your Information secure and to disclose such information only as described in this Privacy Policy. We will hold and transmit your Information in a secure and confidential environment. Your Information will be stored and processed on our computers in the UK. Where your Information is disclosed in accordance with this Privacy Policy, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive the information.  
Business Transitions

In the event that WMG is subjected to a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, your Information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. You will be notified via prominent notice on our website 30 days prior to a change of ownership or control of your Information.

 **Cookies**

To make full use of www.webmarketinggroup.co.uk, your computer, tablet or mobile phone will need to accept cookies.  
Our cookies don’t store sensitive information such as your name or address: they simply hold the ‘key’ that, once you’re signed in, is associated with this information. However, if you’d prefer to restrict, block or delete cookies from www.webmarketinggroup.co.uk, or any other website, you can use your browser to do this. Each browser is different, so check the ‘Help’ menu of your particular browser (or your mobile phone’s handset manual) to learn how to change your cookie preferences.

 **Links**

Our website may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our website and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information from you. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected on this website.

 **Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to amend or modify our Privacy Policy from time to time and such modification shall be effective immediately upon posting of the modified policy on this website. You are responsible for regularly reviewing information posted online to obtain timely notice of such changes. Your continued use of this website after amendments are posted constitutes your acceptance of this policy as modified. If we make substantive changes to this Privacy Policy, we will announce it on our website.

 **Contact Information**

Your privacy is extremely important to us. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our website, please feel free to Contact Us
